[
    {
        "question": "Lake Erie contains an artificial reef made from the pieces of which sports stadium demolished in 1996?",
        "answer": "Cleveland Municipal Stadium"
    },
    {
        "question": "Into what ocean does the Zambezi River flow?",
        "answer": "Indian"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which ocean does the Zambezi River flow into?",
        "answer": "Indian"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which Renaissance City was severely flooded in November 1966?",
        "answer": "Florence"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country built an airport that only landed one commercial aircraft?",
        "answer": "United Kingdom"
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the only airport to serve four countries within an hour`s drive?",
        "answer": "Bratislava, Slovakia"
    },
    {
        "question": "Easter Island is a part of which South American country?",
        "answer": "Chile"
    },
    {
        "question": "Nyala are a type of antelope that are indigenous to which continent?",
        "answer": "Africa"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which country is Great Barrier Island part of?",
        "answer": "New Zealand"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which quarter of New Orleans is famous for its restaurants and jazz clubs?",
        "answer": "French Quarter"
    },
    {
        "question": "What island is the largest of the Canary islands?",
        "answer": "Tenerife"
    },
    {
        "question": "What does the brass plate on Number 10 Downing Street say?",
        "answer": "First Lord of the Admiralty"
    },
    {
        "question": "In what country can you find the islands Sylt, Fohr, and Amrum?",
        "answer": "Germany"
    },
    {
        "question": "In which sea is the island country of Malta?",
        "answer": "Mediterranean"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which is the largest desert in Australia?",
        "answer": "Great Victoria Desert"
    },
    {
        "question": "Africa`s Victoria Falls are on which river?",
        "answer": "Zambezi"
    },
    {
        "question": "If you are in Thailand and cross the bridge over the River Kwai, what country will you be in?",
        "answer": "Myanmar"
    },
    {
        "question": "The city of New Orleans is on which river?",
        "answer": "Mississippi"
    },
    {
        "question": "What geographical partitions is the state of Louisiana divided into instead of counties?",
        "answer": "Parishes"
    },
    {
        "question": "What`s the capital of Senegal?",
        "answer": "Dakar"
    },
    {
        "question": "Dakar is the capital of which country?",
        "answer": "Senegal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Dakar is the capital of which African country?",
        "answer": "Senegal"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which U.S. state named the cherry as its official state fruit?",
        "answer": "Utah -- A 1997 school class campaigned on behalf of cherries, an important crop in Utah, and got the nod from state legislators."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which two European countries are located along Turkey`s northwestern border?",
        "answer": "Greece and Bulgaria -- Turkey also borders three central Asian countries, as well as, three Middle Eastern countries."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which borough has New York City`s only surf beach?",
        "answer": "Queens -- Rockaway Beach, just a subway ride away from Manhattan, is the only surf-able beach in NYC limits."
    },
    {
        "question": "Where is the New York City Marathon start line?",
        "answer": "Staten Island -- It starts at the base of the Verrazano-Narrows Bridge in Staten Island and ends in Central Park."
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the oldest surviving structure in New York City?",
        "answer": "The Wyckoff Farmhouse -- Located in Brooklyn, it was built in 1652 and resembles many early Dutch-American farms of the time."
    },
    {
        "question": "The Plains of Abraham are located in which North American country?",
        "answer": "Canada"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Nauru?",
        "answer": "Yaren"
    },
    {
        "question": "What river flows through the city of Little Rock?",
        "answer": "Arkansas River"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which four states touch at one point?",
        "answer": "Utah, Colorado, Arizona, and New Mexico"
    },
    {
        "question": "What is the capital of Denmark?",
        "answer": "Copenhagen"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state`s flag is the only one with a Union Jack on it?",
        "answer": "Hawaii"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which US state has the shortest Atlantic coastline, at only about 13 miles long?",
        "answer": "New Hampshire"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city is overlooked by a large statue named `Christ the Redeemer`?",
        "answer": "Rio de Janeiro"
    },
    {
        "question": "The city of New Orleans is located in which state?",
        "answer": "Louisiana"
    },
    {
        "question": "What city is nicknamed the `Big Apple`?",
        "answer": "New York City"
    },
    {
        "question": "What US city is home to the Bishop Museum?",
        "answer": "Honolulu"
    },
    {
        "question": "What`s the oldest university in England?",
        "answer": "Oxford University"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which U.S. state has most miles of rivers?",
        "answer": "Nebraska"
    },
    {
        "question": "Mogadishu is the capital of which African country?",
        "answer": "Somalia"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country is the `land of the lions`?",
        "answer": "Singapore"
    },
    {
        "question": "Approximately, how many times larger than Rhode Island is Texas?",
        "answer": "257"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country borders Sierra Leone to the north?",
        "answer": "Guinea"
    },
    {
        "question": "What country borders Guinea to the south?",
        "answer": "Sierra Leone"
    },
    {
        "question": "Sierra Leone lies along the shores of which ocean?",
        "answer": "Atlantic"
    },
    {
        "question": "What year did Sierra Leone gain its independence from the UK?",
        "answer": "1961"
    },
    {
        "question": "What two modern Canadian provinces comprised the `Province of Canada`?",
        "answer": "Quebec and Ontario -- When Canada became its own country in 1867, the Province of Canada was dissolved into the modern-day provinces of Quebec and Ontario."
    },
    {
        "question": "Which South American country has the most Italian speakers?",
        "answer": "Argentina -- It is home to 1.5 million Italian speakers. Italian is the second most widely spoken language in Argentina after Spanish."
    },
    {
        "question": "What three islands are located in the Bay of Naples?",
        "answer": "Capri, Ischia and Procida -- The striking natural beauty of the Bay of Naples and the Amalfi Coast has made this region of Italy a coveted vacation destination for centuries."
    }
]